https://sonatest.com/about/privacy-policy

Skip to content
01908 316345
sales@sonatest.com
Search
About UsOur ExpertiseGlobal CoverageOur PartnersOur PeopleCareersCustomer ServicePrivacy PolicyAnti Bribery & CorruptionIndustriesAerospaceAutomotiveChemicalEducationInfrastructureManufacturingMarineMilitaryMiningOil &
GasPower GenerationRailServiceSpaceProductsUltrasonic Testing (UT)Phased Array Flaw DetectorsThickness GaugesWheelProbesScannersTransducersSoftwareCouplantAccessoriesRadiographicTechnologyNon Destructive ExaminationUltrasonic Non Destructive ExaminationAdvanced TechnologyServicesCalibration & RepairServiceTrainingApplication EvaluationNews And EventsLatest NewsEventsBlogResourcesSonatest Resource Centre (SRC)Applications and SolutionsEducational NotesSonatest YouTube ChannelSonatest Legacy ProductsContact UsGet In TouchProduct Registration FormReturns ProcedureSearch
Search
Privacy Policy
Privacy & Cookies
Sonatest values its visitors’ privacy. This privacy policy summarises what information we might collect from a registered user or other visitor ("you"), and what we will and will not do with it.
What we do with your personally identifiable information
It is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any products or services. "Personally identifiable information" means information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as, for example:
Your name, company, email address, phone number, and address
Your computer’s domain name and IP address, indicating where your computer is located on the Internet
If you do provide personally identifiable information to us, we will:
Neither sell, rent nor provide it to a third party without your permission. We may use your contact information to provide you with information we believe you need to know or may find useful, such as (for example) news about our services and products and modifications to the Terms of Service;
Take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information from loss, misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction;
Not use or disclose the information except:as necessary to provide services or products you have ordered;in other ways described in this privacy policy or to which you have otherwise consented;in the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined (for example, statistical compilations);as required by law, for example, in response to a subpoena or search warrant;to outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential;as necessary to enforce the Terms of Service;as necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of Sonatest Ltd, its users, or others. This may include (for example) exchanging information with other organisations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.
Other information we collect
We may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as (for example) the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate, for technical administration of our website; research and development; customer and account administration; and to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files that are downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Your browser sends these cookies back to the website every time you visit the site again so it can recognise you as a return visitor and improve your experience.
The cookies used on our websites are classified based on the International Chamber of Commerce (ICC) guide for cookie categories. We only use cookies from the "Performance" category which collect information about how you use our website.
There is nothing especially secret about the information gathered by cookies, but you may be concerned that your web behaviour is being used to target you for special offers. For transparency we provide a list of our third party tracking cookies with information about how to opt out of them if you wish.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a service offered by Google that generates detailed statistics about the visitors to a website. Their cookies are used to store details how long a visitor spends on a website and where they came from.
The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on is available for Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Opera. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on
External data storage sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Your privacy responsibilities
To help protect your privacy, be sure to take customary precautions to guard against malware (viruses, Trojan horses, bots, etc.), for example by installing and updating suitable anti-virus software.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy as we deem necessary or appropriate, because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices. If you have provided us with an email address, we will endeavour to notify you, by email to that address, of any material change to how we will use personally identifiable information.
Questions?
If you have questions or comments about our privacy policy, send email to marketing@sonatest.com or call us on 01908 316345.
